<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hiberbee.com/feed/pages.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://hiberbee.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/feed/pages.xml</id><title type="html"> | Pages</title><entry><title type="html">Taxonomy</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/taxonomy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Taxonomy"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/taxonomy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/taxonomy/"></content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry xml:lang="ru"><title type="html">Offer</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/offer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Offer"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/offer</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/offer/">&lt;h1&gt;Публичный договор-оферта&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Общие положения&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;1.1. Физическое лицо-предприниматель Волков Владислав Викторович (далее - Исполнитель), предлагает любому дееспособному лицу (далее - &lt;em&gt;Заказчик&lt;/em&gt;) заключить этот Договор на определенных в нем условиях.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1.2. В соответствии со статьей 633 Гражданского кодекса Украины этот договор является публичной офертой (публичным договором), и в случае принятия его условий (акцепта) Заказчик обязуется добросовестно их выполнять.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1.3. Несогласие с определенными в настоящем Договоре условиями влечет невозможность предоставления Исполнителем услуг обучения.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1.4. Заказчик предоставляет разрешение Исполнителю на обработку своих персональных данных в соответствии с Законом Украины «&lt;a href=&quot;https://zakon.rada.gov.ua/laws/show/2297-17&quot;&gt;О защите персональных данных&lt;/a&gt;{:target=”_blank”}».&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Предмет договора&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;2.1. Исполнитель в соответствии с условиями настоящего Договора предоставляет Заказчику услуги обучения и професиональную консультацию, согласно учебным программам, детальное описание которых содержится на веб-сайте &lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt; (далее - &lt;em&gt;программа&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2.2. Факт оплаты Заказчиком услуг обучения свидетельствует о безусловном принятии Заказчиком условий, определенных в настоящем Договоре.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2.3. Стоимость услуг обучения определяется в зависимости от выбранного Заказчиком тренинга или программы.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;3. Права и обязанноси исполнителя&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h3&gt;3.1. Исполнитель обязуется:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.1.1. На основании настоящего Договора и после оплаты стоимости выбранного Заказчиком учебного плана предоставить ему услуги обучения в срок, определенный указанным планом.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.1.2. Своевременно уведомлять Заказчика о переносе занятий, предусмотренных учебным планом с одновременным уведомлением даты, на которую перенесено указанное занятие.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.1.3. Предоставлять Заказчику услуги согласно условиям настоящего Договора&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;3.2. Исполнитель имеет право:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.1. Приостановить / прекратить предоставление Заказчику услуг обучения в одностороннем порядке в следующих случаях:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Заказчик нарушил условия настоящего Договора;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Заказчик с использованием оборудования Исполнителя совершил действия, которые препятствуют функционированию Интернета или внутренних каналов связи в учебных помещениях, в том числе действия незаконного или аморального характера, или нарушающие общественный порядок, посягающие на честь и достоинство граждан и предприятий и/или вызывают их жалобы, распространения в сети вирусов или других нежелательных компонентов, совершение действий, направленных на получение конфиденциальной информации или информации со специальным доступом;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Небрежного отношения Заказчика к имуществу и/или оборудования Исполнителя, повлекшее его повреждения.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.2. В одностороннем порядке расторгнуть настоящий Договор досрочно в случае невыполнения Заказчиком его условий, в частности пунктов 4.1.1, 4.1.4 - 4.1.7 настоящего Договора, и/или систематического невыполнения Заказчиком правил поведения.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.3. Вносить в одностороннем порядке изменения в настоящий Договор, а также учебные планы и стоимость услуг обучения с предварительной их публикацией на сайте &lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt;. При этом внесение изменений в учебные планы и стоимости услуг обучения, при предоставлении Заказчику услуг обучения не допускается.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.4. Требовать от Заказчика возмещения ущерба, причиненного действиями Заказчика.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.5. Переносить занятия, предусмотренные учебным планом, с одного дня на другой, но своевременно при этом предупредив Заказчика не менее, чем за сутки.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.2.6. Не допускать Заказчика к обучению в состоянии алкогольного и/или наркотического опьянения.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. Права и обязанности заказчика&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h3&gt;4.1. Заказчик обязан:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.1. Добросовестно выполнять условия настоящего Договора, соблюдать правила поведения и своевременно внести плату за услуги обучения по выбранному учебному плану.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.2. Вовремя появляться в помещении, в котором предоставляются услуги обучения, а в случае отсутствия на занятии Заказчик лишается права предъявления каких-либо претензий относительно недополученной вследствие этого услуги.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.3. Заблаговременно сообщать о своем отсутствии на занятиях. Плата за пропущенные Заказчиком занятия, предусмотренные учебным планом, не возвращается.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.4. В ходе получения услуг обучения выполнять законные требования Исполнителя, не являться на занятия в состоянии алкогольного и/или наркотического опьянения, проявлять уважение к окружающим.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.5. Бережно относиться к имуществу и оборудованию Исполнителя, возмещать любые убытки Исполнителю, вызванные действиями Заказчика.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.6. Не публиковать, не передавать третьим лицам и не использовать в коммерческих целях методические материалы, предоставляемые Заказчику в ходе предоставления ему услуг обучения, в том числе для самостоятельной работы.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.1.7. Не производить видеозапись и аудиозапись курса или их частей, в коммерческих или иных целях без письменного согласия Исполнителя.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;4.2. Заказчик имеет право:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.2.1. Получать услуги обучения, предусмотренные настоящим Договором.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.2.2. Требовать соблюдения Исполнителем условий настоящего Договора.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.2.3. Вносить оплату Исполнителю за услуги обучения, согласно выбранному учебному плану, любым из предусмотренных действующим законодательством Украины способом.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4.2.4. Расторгнуть настоящий Договор в одностороннем порядке при условии предварительного уведомления об этом Исполнителя за два дня.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Порядок расчетов&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;5.1. Услуги обучения по настоящему Договору предоставляются исключительно на условиях 100-процентной предоплаты их стоимости по конкретному учебному плану.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5.2. Все расчеты осуществляются в национальной валюте Украины - гривне.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5.3. Исполнитель не несет ответственности за порядок перечисления/зачисления средств.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5.4. Моментом оплаты считается момент зачисления денежных средств на расчетный счет Исполнителя или получения наличных средств Исполнителем.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;6. Ответственность&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.1. За неисполнение или ненадлежащее исполнение условий настоящего Договора Исполнитель и Заказчик несут ответственность, предусмотренную настоящим Договором и действующим законодательством Украины.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.2. Заказчик осознает, что нарушение им условий настоящего Договора приводит к его расторжению Исполнителем в одностороннем порядке с последующим прекращением/приостановлением оказания услуг обучения.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.3. Исполнитель принимает на себя полную ответственность в соответствии с требованиями Закона Украины «&lt;a href=&quot;https://zakon.rada.gov.ua/laws/show/2297-17&quot;&gt;О защите персональных данных&lt;/a&gt;{:target=”_blank”}».&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.4. Заказчик принимает на себя полную ответственность за риски, связанные с использованием имущества и оборудования Исполнителя.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.5. Исполнитель не несет ответственности за неотредактированные методические материалы, которые передаются Заказчику при оказании ему услуг обучения по выбранному учебному плану, в том числе для самостоятельной работы.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.6. Заказчик несет полную ответственность за незаконный доступ и осуществления несанкционированного вмешательства в работу компьютеров, систем и компьютерной сети в соответствии с действующим законодательством Украины.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6.7. В случае нарушения Заказчиком условий Договора Исполнитель освобождается от выполнения взятых на себя обязательств по настоящему Договору.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;7. Форс-мажор&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;7.1. Исполнитель и Заказчик освобождаются от ответственности за полное или частичное неисполнение своих обязательств по настоящему Договору, если это явилось следствием обстоятельств непреодолимой силы, возникших после вступления в силу настоящего Договора в результате событий чрезвычайного характера, которые не могли быть предусмотрены и которые невозможно было предотвратить разумными мерами.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;8. Срок действия договора&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;8.1. Договор вступает в силу с момента оплаты услуг обучения Заказчиком Исполнителю и действует в течение всего срока, определенного в выбранном Заказчиком учебном плане.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;8.2. Настоящий Договор может быть прекращен (расторгнут) по соглашению Заказчика и Исполнителя, оформленного в письменном виде.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;9. Разрешение споров&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;9.1. Все споры и разногласия, возникшие по поводу выполнения условий настоящего Договора, подлежат разрешению путем переговоров на основании письменного заявления (претензии) Заказчика, с добавлением чека (квитанции) об оплате услуг обучения.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9.2. Исполнитель после получения от Заказчика услуг заявления (претензии), обязан в течение 20 (двадцати) дней удовлетворить заявленные требования или направить Заказчику мотивированный отказ.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9.3. В случае если спор, который возник, не будет урегулирован в претензионном порядке, Заказчик или Исполнитель имеет право обратиться в суд по месту нахождения Исполнителя.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9.4. Заказчик услуг гарантирует, что все условия настоящего Договора ему понятны, и он принимает их безусловно и в полном объеме.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;10. Адреса и реквизиты&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Исполнитель&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; ФЛП Волков Владислав Викторович&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; Адрес: 53407, г. Марганец, ул Крымская, 4&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; Код ЕГРПОУ: 3224403735&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; р/р: 26000606297 “Райффайзен Банк Аваль”&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; МФО: 380805&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; № плательщика ЕСВ: 0421036242&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; Плательщик единого налога 5%&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Публичный договор-оферта</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Projects</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/projects/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Projects"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/projects</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/projects/">&lt;h1&gt;Проекты&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Проекты</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">People</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/people/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="People"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/people</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/people/"></content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry xml:lang="ru"><title type="html">Gratitude</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gratitude"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/gratitude</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/gratitude/"></content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry xml:lang="ru"><title type="html">Faq</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/faq/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Faq"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/faq</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/faq/">&lt;h1&gt;Часто задаваемые вопросы&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Часто задаваемые вопросы</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="ru"><title type="html">О проекте</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="О проекте"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/about</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/about/">&lt;h1&gt;О проекте&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;Меня зовут Владислав, и этот проект - результат трансформации моих знаний, опыта и прецедентов из практики технического консультирования - в обучающие программы, с целью поддержки, супервайзинга и формирования лучших инженерных и архитектурных практик.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Чем именно и кому я могу быть полезен, поможет понять мой прошлый опыт, специализация, профессиональные ценности и инсайты.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Аккаунты&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://linkedin.com/in/vladyslavvolkov&quot;&gt;Linkedin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Профиль и квалификация&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;разработка&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;системный дизайн и архитектура&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;технический консалтинг&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;супервайзинг и трансформация технических специалистов в T-shape&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Методологии и практики&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Dev/Ops&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;extreme programming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;CI/CD&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;12 factor-apps&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;BDD&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Основные бизнес-домены&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;automotive&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;government services&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;e-commerce&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;gambling&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;media-services&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;video-on-demand&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;streaming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;analytics&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;enterprise systems.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Ключевые компетенции и специализация&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;software design: Microservices, CQRS, Client-Server, ADR&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;development: JVM (Java Spring-Hibernate/Kotlin/Groovy/Scala), Web (PHP/Python/Ruby/NodeJS/TS), Scripting (Bash/Gradle &amp;amp; Kotlin DSL)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;operations: Cloud Native (service orchestration, mesh, runtime, provisioning)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;testing: xUnit, Cucumber, Gatling&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Статистика&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Языки программирования за последний год&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/misc/languages-year.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Used programming languages&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Программирование за последний год&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/misc/waka-year.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Programming stats&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Инсайты&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;В разное время открыл для себя, что:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Обучение - взаимовыгодная инвестиция для обеих сторон&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Самым ценным для клиентов оказался опыт чужих неудач&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;С повышением уровня все сложнее становится найти ментора&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/misc/knowledge-experience-strategy.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Knowledge, experience, strategy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Если наши области компетенции пересекаются, у вас уже есть знания, но вам нужен опыт и стратегия идти дальше, я буду рад помочь.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">О проекте Меня зовут Владислав, и этот проект - результат трансформации моих знаний, опыта и прецедентов из практики технического консультирования - в обучающие программы, с целью поддержки, супервайзинга и формирования лучших инженерных и архитектурных практик.</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Terms Of Use</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/terms-of-use/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Terms Of Use"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/terms-of-use</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/terms-of-use/">&lt;h1&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;Version 1.0 The Hiberbee website located at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt; is a copyrighted work belonging to Hiberbee. Certain features of the Site may be subject to additional guidelines, terms, or rules, which will be posted on the Site in connection with such features. All such additional terms, guidelines, and rules are incorporated by reference into these Terms. These Terms of Use described the legally binding terms and conditions that oversee your use of the Site. BY LOGGING INTO THE SITE, YOU ARE BEING COMPLIANT THAT THESE TERMS and you represent that you have the authority and capacity to enter into these Terms. YOU SHOULD BE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OF AGE TO ACCESS THE SITE. IF YOU DISAGREE WITH ALL OF THE PROVISION OF THESE TERMS, DO NOT LOG INTO AND/OR USE THE SITE. These terms require the use of arbitration Section 10.2 on an individual basis to resolve disputes and also limit the remedies available to you in the event of a dispute. These Terms of Use were created with the help of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.termsofusegenerator.net&quot;&gt;Terms Of Use Generator&lt;/a&gt;{:target=”_blank”} and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.privacy-policy-template.com&quot;&gt;Privacy Policy Template&lt;/a&gt;{:target=”_blank”}.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Access to the Site&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subject to these Terms.&lt;/strong&gt; Company grants you a non-transferable, non-exclusive, revocable, limited license to access the Site solely for your own personal, noncommercial use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certain Restrictions.&lt;/strong&gt; The rights approved to you in these Terms are subject to the following restrictions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;you shall not sell, rent, lease, transfer, assign, distribute, host, or otherwise commercially exploit the Site;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;you shall not change, make derivative works of, disassemble, reverse compile or reverse engineer any part of the Site;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;you shall not access the Site in order to build a similar or competitive website;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;except as expressly stated herein, no part of the Site may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted or transmitted in any form or by any means unless otherwise indicated, any future release, update, or other addition to functionality of the Site shall be subject to these Terms.  All copyright and other proprietary notices on the Site must be retained on all copies thereof.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Company reserves the right to change, suspend, or cease the Site with or without notice to you.  You approved that Company will not be held liable to you or any third-party for any change, interruption, or termination of the Site or any part.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Support or Maintenance.&lt;/strong&gt; You agree that Company will have no obligation to provide you with any support in connection with the Site.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Excluding any User Content that you may provide, you are aware that all the intellectual property rights, including copyrights, patents, trademarks, and trade secrets, in the Site and its content are owned by Company or Company’s suppliers. Note that these Terms and access to the Site do not give you any rights, title or interest in or to any intellectual property rights, except for the limited access rights expressed in Section 2.1. Company and its suppliers reserve all rights not granted in these Terms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads; Other Users&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads.&lt;/strong&gt; The Site may contain links to third-party websites and services, and/or display advertisements for third-parties.  Such Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads are not under the control of Company, and Company is not responsible for any Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads.  Company provides access to these Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads only as a convenience to you, and does not review, approve, monitor, endorse, warrant, or make any representations with respect to Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads.  You use all Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads at your own risk, and should apply a suitable level of caution and discretion in doing so. When you click on any of the Third-Party Links &amp;amp; Ads, the applicable third party’s terms and policies apply, including the third party’s privacy and data gathering practices.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Users.&lt;/strong&gt; Each Site user is solely responsible for any and all of its own User Content.  Because we do not control User Content, you acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for any User Content, whether provided by you or by others.  You agree that Company will not be responsible for any loss or damage incurred as the result of any such interactions.  If there is a dispute between you and any Site user, we are under no obligation to become involved.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You hereby release and forever discharge the Company and our officers, employees, agents, successors, and assigns from, and hereby waive and relinquish, each and every past, present and future dispute, claim, controversy, demand, right, obligation, liability, action and cause of action of every kind and nature, that has arisen or arises directly or indirectly out of, or that relates directly or indirectly to, the Site. If you are a California resident, you hereby waive California civil code section 1542 in connection with the foregoing, which states: “a general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his or her favor at the time of executing the release, which if known by him or her must have materially affected his or her settlement with the debtor.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Disclaimers&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The site is provided on an “as-is” and “as available” basis, and company and our suppliers expressly disclaim any and all warranties and conditions of any kind, whether express, implied, or statutory, including all warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, quiet enjoyment, accuracy, or non-infringement.  We and our suppliers make not guarantee that the site will meet your requirements, will be available on an uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free basis, or will be accurate, reliable, free of viruses or other harmful code, complete, legal, or safe.  If applicable law requires any warranties with respect to the site, all such warranties are limited in duration to ninety (90) days from the date of first use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.  Some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts, so the above limitation may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Limitation on Liability&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;To the maximum extent permitted by law, in no event shall company or our suppliers be liable to you or any third-party for any lost profits, lost data, costs of procurement of substitute products, or any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, special or punitive damages arising from or relating to these terms or your use of, or incapability to use the site even if company has been advised of the possibility of such damages.  Access to and use of the site is at your own discretion and risk, and you will be solely responsible for any damage to your device or computer system, or loss of data resulting therefrom.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To the maximum extent permitted by law, notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained herein, our liability to you for any damages arising from or related to this agreement, will at all times be limited to a maximum of fifty U.S. dollars (u.s. $50). The existence of more than one claim will not enlarge this limit.  You agree that our suppliers will have no liability of any kind arising from or relating to this agreement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some jurisdictions do not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Term and Termination.&lt;/strong&gt; Subject to this Section, these Terms will remain in full force and effect while you use the Site.  We may suspend or terminate your rights to use the Site at any time for any reason at our sole discretion, including for any use of the Site in violation of these Terms.  Upon termination of your rights under these Terms, your Account and right to access and use the Site will terminate immediately.  You understand that any termination of your Account may involve deletion of your User Content associated with your Account from our live databases.  Company will not have any liability whatsoever to you for any termination of your rights under these Terms.  Even after your rights under these Terms are terminated, the following provisions of these Terms will remain in effect: Sections 2 through 2.5, Section 3 and Sections 4 through 10.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Copyright Policy&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Company respects the intellectual property of others and asks that users of our Site do the same.  In connection with our Site, we have adopted and implemented a policy respecting copyright law that provides for the removal of any infringing materials and for the termination of users of our online Site who are repeated infringers of intellectual property rights, including copyrights.  If you believe that one of our users is, through the use of our Site, unlawfully infringing the copyright(s) in a work, and wish to have the allegedly infringing material removed, the following information in the form of a written notification (pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)) must be provided to our designated Copyright Agent:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;your physical or electronic signature;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;identification of the copyrighted work(s) that you claim to have been infringed;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;identification of the material on our services that you claim is infringing and that you request us to remove;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;sufficient information to permit us to locate such material;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;a statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the objectionable material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or under the law; and&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;a statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are either the owner of the copyright that has allegedly been infringed or that you are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please note that, pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(f), any misrepresentation of material fact in a written notification automatically subjects the complaining party to liability for any damages, costs and attorney’s fees incurred by us in connection with the written notification and allegation of copyright infringement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;General&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;These Terms are subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes, we may notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site.  You are responsible for providing us with your most current e-mail address.  In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.  Any changes to these Terms will be effective upon the earliest of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Site.  These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Site.  Continued use of our Site following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. Dispute Resolution. Please read this Arbitration Agreement carefully. It is part of your contract with Company and affects your rights.  It contains procedures for MANDATORY BINDING ARBITRATION AND A CLASS ACTION WAIVER.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applicability of Arbitration Agreement.&lt;/strong&gt; All claims and disputes in connection with the Terms or the use of any product or service provided by the Company that cannot be resolved informally or in small claims court shall be resolved by binding arbitration on an individual basis under the terms of this Arbitration Agreement.  Unless otherwise agreed to, all arbitration proceedings shall be held in English.  This Arbitration Agreement applies to you and the Company, and to any subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, employees, predecessors in interest, successors, and assigns, as well as all authorized or unauthorized users or beneficiaries of services or goods provided under the Terms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice Requirement and Informal Dispute Resolution.&lt;/strong&gt; Before either party may seek arbitration, the party must first send to the other party a written Notice of Dispute describing the nature and basis of the claim or dispute, and the requested relief.  A Notice to the Company should be sent to: 3 Lva Tovstoho St., Kyiv, 01004, Kyiv region, Ukraine. After the Notice is received, you and the Company may attempt to resolve the claim or dispute informally.  If you and the Company do not resolve the claim or dispute within thirty (30) days after the Notice is received, either party may begin an arbitration proceeding.  The amount of any settlement offer made by any party may not be disclosed to the arbitrator until after the arbitrator has determined the amount of the award to which either party is entitled.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arbitration Rules.&lt;/strong&gt; Arbitration shall be initiated through the American Arbitration Association, an established alternative dispute resolution provider that offers arbitration as set forth in this section.  If AAA is not available to arbitrate, the parties shall agree to select an alternative ADR Provider.  The rules of the ADR Provider shall govern all aspects of the arbitration except to the extent such rules are in conflict with the Terms.  The AAA Consumer Arbitration Rules governing the arbitration are available online at adr.org or by calling the AAA at 1-800-778-7879.  The arbitration shall be conducted by a single, neutral arbitrator.  Any claims or disputes where the total amount of the award sought is less than Ten Thousand U.S. Dollars (US $10,000.00) may be resolved through binding non-appearance-based arbitration, at the option of the party seeking relief.  For claims or disputes where the total amount of the award sought is Ten Thousand U.S. Dollars (US $10,000.00) or more, the right to a hearing will be determined by the Arbitration Rules.  Any hearing will be held in a location within 100 miles of your residence, unless you reside outside of the United States, and unless the parties agree otherwise.  If you reside outside of the U.S., the arbitrator shall give the parties reasonable notice of the date, time and place of any oral hearings. Any judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction.  If the arbitrator grants you an award that is greater than the last settlement offer that the Company made to you prior to the initiation of arbitration, the Company will pay you the greater of the award or $2,500.00.  Each party shall bear its own costs and disbursements arising out of the arbitration and shall pay an equal share of the fees and costs of the ADR Provider.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Rules for Non-Appearance Based Arbitration.&lt;/strong&gt; If non-appearance based arbitration is elected, the arbitration shall be conducted by telephone, online and/or based solely on written submissions; the specific manner shall be chosen by the party initiating the arbitration.  The arbitration shall not involve any personal appearance by the parties or witnesses unless otherwise agreed by the parties.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time Limits.&lt;/strong&gt; If you or the Company pursues arbitration, the arbitration action must be initiated and/or demanded within the statute of limitations and within any deadline imposed under the AAA Rules for the pertinent claim.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authority of Arbitrator.&lt;/strong&gt; If arbitration is initiated, the arbitrator will decide the rights and liabilities of you and the Company, and the dispute will not be consolidated with any other matters or joined with any other cases or parties.  The arbitrator shall have the authority to grant motions dispositive of all or part of any claim.  The arbitrator shall have the authority to award monetary damages, and to grant any non-monetary remedy or relief available to an individual under applicable law, the AAA Rules, and the Terms.  The arbitrator shall issue a written award and statement of decision describing the essential findings and conclusions on which the award is based.  The arbitrator has the same authority to award relief on an individual basis that a judge in a court of law would have.  The award of the arbitrator is final and binding upon you and the Company.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waiver of Jury Trial.&lt;/strong&gt; THE PARTIES HEREBY WAIVE THEIR CONSTITUTIONAL AND STATUTORY RIGHTS TO GO TO COURT AND HAVE A TRIAL IN FRONT OF A JUDGE OR A JURY, instead electing that all claims and disputes shall be resolved by arbitration under this Arbitration Agreement.  Arbitration procedures are typically more limited, more efficient and less expensive than rules applicable in a court and are subject to very limited review by a court.  In the event any litigation should arise between you and the Company in any state or federal court in a suit to vacate or enforce an arbitration award or otherwise, YOU AND THE COMPANY WAIVE ALL RIGHTS TO A JURY TRIAL, instead electing that the dispute be resolved by a judge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waiver of Class or Consolidated Actions.&lt;/strong&gt; All claims and disputes within the scope of this arbitration agreement must be arbitrated or litigated on an individual basis and not on a class basis, and claims of more than one customer or user cannot be arbitrated or litigated jointly or consolidated with those of any other customer or user.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confidentiality.&lt;/strong&gt; All aspects of the arbitration proceeding shall be strictly confidential.  The parties agree to maintain confidentiality unless otherwise required by law.  This paragraph shall not prevent a party from submitting to a court of law any information necessary to enforce this Agreement, to enforce an arbitration award, or to seek injunctive or equitable relief.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severability.&lt;/strong&gt; If any part or parts of this Arbitration Agreement are found under the law to be invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, then such specific part or parts shall be of no force and effect and shall be severed and the remainder of the Agreement shall continue in full force and effect.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right to Waive.&lt;/strong&gt; Any or all of the rights and limitations set forth in this Arbitration Agreement may be waived by the party against whom the claim is asserted.  Such waiver shall not waive or affect any other portion of this Arbitration Agreement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survival of Agreement.&lt;/strong&gt; This Arbitration Agreement will survive the termination of your relationship with Company.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Small Claims Court.&lt;/strong&gt; Nonetheless the foregoing, either you or the Company may bring an individual action in small claims court.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emergency Equitable Relief.&lt;/strong&gt; Anyhow the foregoing, either party may seek emergency equitable relief before a state or federal court in order to maintain the status quo pending arbitration.  A request for interim measures shall not be deemed a waiver of any other rights or obligations under this Arbitration Agreement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Claims Not Subject to Arbitration.&lt;/strong&gt; Notwithstanding the foregoing, claims of defamation, violation of the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act, and infringement or misappropriation of the other party’s patent, copyright, trademark or trade secrets shall not be subject to this Arbitration Agreement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In any circumstances where the foregoing Arbitration Agreement permits the parties to litigate in court, the parties hereby agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located within Netherlands County, California, for such purposes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Site may be subject to U.S. export control laws and may be subject to export or import regulations in other countries. You agree not to export, re-export, or transfer, directly or indirectly, any U.S. technical data acquired from Company, or any products utilizing such data, in violation of the United States export laws or regulations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Company is located at the address in Section 10.8. If you are a California resident, you may report complaints to the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Product of the California Department of Consumer Affairs by contacting them in writing at 400 R Street, Sacramento, CA 95814, or by telephone at (800) 952-5210.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electronic Communications.&lt;/strong&gt; The communications between you and Company use electronic means, whether you use the Site or send us emails, or whether Company posts notices on the Site or communicates with you via email. For contractual purposes, you (a) consent to receive communications from Company in an electronic form; and (b) agree that all terms and conditions, agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that Company provides to you electronically satisfy any legal obligation that such communications would satisfy if it were be in a hard copy writing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entire Terms.&lt;/strong&gt; These Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and us regarding the use of the Site. Our failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms shall not operate as a waiver of such right or provision. The section titles in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect. The word “including” means “including without limitation”. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable, the other provisions of these Terms will be unimpaired and the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed modified so that it is valid and enforceable to the maximum extent permitted by law.  Your relationship to Company is that of an independent contractor, and neither party is an agent or partner of the other.  These Terms, and your rights and obligations herein, may not be assigned, subcontracted, delegated, or otherwise transferred by you without Company’s prior written consent, and any attempted assignment, subcontract, delegation, or transfer in violation of the foregoing will be null and void.  Company may freely assign these Terms.  The terms and conditions set forth in these Terms shall be binding upon assignees.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Privacy.&lt;/strong&gt; Please read &lt;a href=&quot;https://privacypolicytemplate.net&quot;&gt;our Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Copyright/Trademark Information.&lt;/strong&gt; Copyright ©. All rights reserved.  All trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on the Site are our property or the property of other third-parties. You are not permitted to use these Marks without our prior written consent or the consent of such third party which may own the Marks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Terms of Use</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Privacy Policy</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/privacy-policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Privacy Policy"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/privacy-policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/privacy-policy/">&lt;h1&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Your privacy is critically important to us&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is Hiberbee’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt; (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “&lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt;”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources. This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Website Visitors&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Like most website operators, Hiberbee collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Hiberbee’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Hiberbee’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Hiberbee may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Hiberbee also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on &lt;a href=&quot;https://hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;https://hiberbee.com&lt;/a&gt; blog posts. Hiberbee only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Links To External Sites&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Credit &amp;amp; Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This privacy policy was created at &lt;a href=&quot;https://termsandconditionstemplate.com/privacy-policy-generator/&quot;&gt;Privacy policy template generator&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@hiberbee.com&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Privacy Policy</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Страница не найдена</title><link href="https://hiberbee.com/404.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Страница не найдена"/><published>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</published><updated>2019-06-09T18:02:40+03:00</updated><id>https://hiberbee.com/not-found</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://hiberbee.com/404.html">&lt;h1&gt;Страница не найдена&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Страница не найдена</summary></entry></feed>